erayo.com 2009-06-19

# Privacy Policy

Last Revised: October 17, 2007 

Erayo Ltd. ("Erayo") respects your privacy and is fully committed to protecting the personal  
information that you share with it. Erayo believes that its registered users ("Erayo  
Members") have a full right to know its policies and practices regarding the information  
Erayo collects while visiting and using its website at the address [http://www.erayo.com](http://www.erayo.com/)   
(the "Website") and System (as such term is define in Seller Terms of Use and   
Erayo Buyer Terms of Use ). The guidelines contained herein (the "Privacy  
Policy") apply only to the Website and System operated by or for Erayo, and it is not  
applicable for any other business which Erayo may have. 

By using the Website and System you agree to the terms and conditions set forth in this  
Privacy Policy. 

Erayo collects personal information provided consciously and voluntarily by Erayo  
Members during the creation and activation of an Account (as such term is defined in  
Erayo Seller Terms of Use and Erayo Terms of Use ) via the Website  
(the "Registration Process"). "Personal Information” means individually identifiable  
information such as the name, telephone number, email address, financial information  
such as bank account and credit card details, and other information collected during your  
use of the Website, the System and other services provided to you by Erayo. The  
Personal Information is collected for the purpose of creating an Account associated with   
the Erayo Member, in order to provide Erayo Members with a user friendly and time  
saving system for carrying out their transactions. Erayo will keep the information the Erayo  
Member provided during the Registration Process, until the Erayo Member requests   
cancellation of his Account and membership. 

Erayo may use the Personal Information in order to: 

(a) Provide certain services. 

(b) Process Orders (as this such term is defined in Erayo Seller Terms of Use and  
Erayo Buyer Terms of Use) and transactions and send notices to Erayo  
Members of such. 

(c) Provide customer support.

(d) Provide targeted marketing material, service update notices, and promotional  
offers based upon Erayo Members' preferences.

(e) Resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems. 

Erayo also collects non-personal and non-identifiable information ("Non-Personal   
Information") from its Erayo Members. Non-Personal Information is unconcealed   
information which is available to Erayo while Erayo Members are connected to the   
Website or the System. Non-Personal Information may contain the identity of an Erayo   
Member's browsing system and operating system, the order of the pages Erayo Members   
visited, the time and date of an Erayo Member's connection and the like. This type of   
information is collected for statistical purposes and is used for customization and   
improvement of Erayo's services, System and Website interface. 

Erayo will not share any information it collects with any other party, except in the  
following cases: (a) an Erayo Member gave his explicit consent for such transfer prior to  
the transfer; (b) sharing and transferring Personal Information is required in order to  
process the Order (as this such term is defined in Erayo Seller Terms of Use and Erayo   
Buyer Terms of Use) and/or to provide other services requested by the relevant Erayo   
Member; or (c) the transfer of information is required by law or by a court   
order. For avoidance of doubt, Erayo may transfer Non-personal Information to   
third-parties at its own discretion. 

Erayo Members can access their personal Account and make changes to the information   
in it. However, Erayo Members are not permitted to change the username or shop name   
they selected when they registered with the Website.

For instructions on how to request change of any personal information you have provided   
to Erayo, please send an email to [support@erayo.com](mailto:support@erayo.com)

While visiting the Websites, Erayo may use an industry-wide technology called   
"Cookies" which stores certain information on your computer. Cookies are small text   
files that can be retrieved only by the website that created them. Cookies will allow Erayo   
to enable automatic sign-in to the Website, so that a registered user shall be regarded as an   
Erayo Member and not as a Viewer (as this term is defined in Erayo Viewer Terms of   
Use). Most Internet browsers will allow you to erase Cookies from your computer,   
block the acceptance of Cookies, or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored.   
However, if you block or erase Cookies, your online experience may be limited.   
Please refer to your browser instructions or “Help” screen to learn more about these   
functions. 

Erayo takes great care in implementing and maintaining the security of its Members'   
Personal Information. Erayo employs industry standard procedures and policies to ensure   
the safety of its Members’ information, and prevent unauthorized use of any such   
information. Among other measures, Erayo protects a Member's Personal Information   
through the use of Fire Wall, encrypted protocol (SSL), encrypted data, and restricted access to   
personal information database. However, Erayo does not guarantee that unauthorized   
access will never occur. Erayo Members are required to maintain the secrecy of their   
login and account information, and are encouraged to change their password from time to   
time. 

The terms of this Privacy Policy will govern the use of the Website the System and any   
information collected therein. Erayo reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at   
anytime, and it asks its Erayo Members to re-visit this page as often as possible. In case   
of any material change, Erayo may replace the "Privacy Policy" link on the home page of   
the Website with a link titled "Updated Privacy Policy dated November 12, 2007." Changes to this   
Privacy Policy are effective as of the stated "Last Revised” date and your continued use   
of the Website after the Last Revised date will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to   
be bound by those changes. 

Inside the Website, you may find links to other websites that are not a part of Erayo's   
Website ("Third-Party Sites"). These sites are independent sites, and Erayo assumes no   
responsibility or liability for them with regard to privacy matters or any other legal   
matter. Erayo Members are encouraged to read the privacy policies of the Third-Party   
Sites. 

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to send   
an email to [support@erayo.com](mailto:support@erayo.com).
